I just want to say, whoever's telling y'all, like, don't waste your time clowning ICE agents, etc.
Like, they don't care.
Yes, they do.
That whole legion is made up of cats who couldn't get any puss in high school.
Who were clowned.
Who went to freaking CrossFit so they could feel like a man.
And who have mini, miniature penises.
And if not that, mini, miniature skill with them.
They are totally and utterly comprised of insecurity.
They are made of weakness.
Their cellular structures are feeble.
The walls of their nuclei are made of phylo paper.
So, yes, clown them, break them, and stop calling them by their names.
They don't deserve that.
All slaves.
And you love it.
So you deserve what you get.
The erosion of your democracy.
You'll soon be the laughing stock of the world.
That works out for less than 50 cents a month.
It's a damn shame.
That's why the children are occupying space in New York, in Boston, in Washington, in Chicago, in San Francisco, in other cities.
Why?
Because they're not looking to you as a source of information for them.
Look how long it took you all to talk about what was going on in New York.
It took you two weeks because the same people that controlled the banks controlled the media.
You all know it, but you're afraid to say it.